|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Alchemy
Shower
Master, it's me, Yeom
Yesterday was a hundred days since you meditated
It's time to go outside
Master
Master...
Master!
- Poor boy
- Poor thing
- Holy Heavens
- Incredible
- He must have frozen to death
- It seems so
- I feel so sorry for him
- Poor baby
- It's a pity
- How so?
What's going on here? What is this?
Homeless boy died
He was just a child. I feel so sorry for him
How can this be?
Just like you always wanted
I will quietly say goodbye to you, master
I feel so sorry for him
He seems to be an orphan
Shall we hold a funeral for him?
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
- Yes
- Let's
Maybe cremate...
and scatter the ashes over Gyeongjeongdaeho Lake?
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
Boy...
are you okay?
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee, Alina
- Well...
- How...
-Where is he going?
-Where are you going?
Stand!
Child
Did you just tell me to stop?
What a fool!
I can't believe you already burned my body
What are you talking about?
If I had come a little later, you would have burned my cane too.
Fool!
M-master?
I just left my body for a while
to check if I have reached Hwangsu
after one hundred days of meditation
But I noticed that my body was burning, so I quickly moved into another
But it's too late
So are you in this boy's body?
Is it really you, master?
Exactly
I am Lee Chul, your master
Here we go...
Master
I'm a nomad
Your Majesty
Didn't you call me to find the nomad?
That's exactly what I'll do
I can
recognize nomads
Has anyone else seen your face?
This is an umbrella
Can be used as a cane
No
In the capital no one else knows that I am sighted
People will think that bandits fought here
You should have stopped looking for me
So I
So Yi, is that you?
I am Kim from Sari village
You made a mistake
We barely know each other. He hardly knows me
About that man
need to take care
There was no need to kill him
If he had gone to Sari, we would never have met again
But you met
Sari Village?
Is that where you stayed?
I was hiding there
Hiding from these thugs
Is there anyone left there who might recognize you?
I didn’t get close to anyone so that they wouldn’t recognize me
I was a thief there
- What is this?
- Money
It will be suspicious if the money doesn't disappear
Keep it for yourself
I didn't mean to harm anyone from Sari Village
Moo Dok in the capital
If we meet, will we have to kill her?
Trader Kim from Sari Village is here?
Yes, he just arrived
He's in the last room on the second floor
Madam?
What brought you to this place?
It's none of your business. You haven't seen me here
Madam, are you really playing?
into gambling?
What? Gambling?
Who do you take me for? Am I some kind of simpleton, in your opinion?
No, of course
But you lied to me when you said the jade wasn't broken
Considering your ability to lie without a twinge of conscience,
I thought maybe you have a talent for gambling too
I came to the seller for tickets
Tickets for the show were sold out
That's why I came here
Entrance ticket
Magi Seochon
- You have two tickets
- I'm going with my mom
Don't tell anyone you saw me here
I don't want any misunderstanding
How to know
You see, I'm not as good at lying as you are.
If someone asks, I'm not sure I could lie
But for your sake I will try
I was lucky enough to meet her here
Why is the head of Sosnovy Bor here?
I hope he's not here for the tickets.
Then I won't be able to go to the show with Dong Gu.
It's you
killed him
It's not me
Why did you kill him?
It's really not me
He was already dead when I arrived
He was killed not long ago
He was killed with one blow
Master Swordsman
I swear it wasn't me
I don't even have a sword
I think one person killed them
Who are these men?
These are thugs who arrived in the capital recently
They have arrived
with trader Kim from the village of Sari?
No
But I remember those thugs picking a fight with him a couple of days ago
They wanted to know where the fraudster who lived in Sari was located.
Sari scammer?
Maybe it's Moo Deok?
Where is she?
He was here
She ran away
What's going on?
What were these bodies?
They wanted to know where the fraudster who lived in Sari was located.
Could they have meant me?
What kind of life did Moo Deok live?
Have you met So Yi?
I wonder what she did this time
Don't mess with her
So Yi...
Who is So Yi?
I haven't seen her myself
But she quarreled with all the guards, and even slapped one in the face
I'm sure they remembered her face
Madam, not a single guard came today
- They both didn’t come?
- Yes
Strange. They never miss work
We're sorry. We shouldn't have treated the magician like that
But is this really necessary?
"Magu"?
Did you lie about being a magician?
I'll be him soon
And even more powerful than you
How dare a fake talk to me like that?
I'll talk down to you
and you will treat me with respect. Isn't it?
Run after him
It's your job
There is a girl in Jwiseonru named Moo Deok from Sari Village?
Yes, I know her. Were you looking for her that night?
I wanted to ask her for a favor and return something.
Moo Deok is not in Jwiseonru
She is a maid in the Jang family, which is Gwangju Jeonbugwan's family.
Is she a maid?
Looks like she really can see now
She probably fooled you too
They brought her to Chwisonra, they thought she was blind,
But everyone was surprised when she opened her eyes and ran away
But she's not a fraud like me
How can she see?
Please don't kill me
I'm sorry
You saw my face, I can't leave you alive
Please...
If she could see then she could recognize me
Is she a maid of the Chang family?
I have to visit her
Did Moo Deok commit murder?
Several men were killed in the inn
Moo Deok was there
But Moo Deok is not strong enough to kill anyone
Especially a few men
This was done by a skilled swordsman
If it's not her
a magician must have helped her
Just don't say
that you suspect our master
No
Wook is now in the palace with Master Li
Thank heavens
It couldn't be Moo Deok
She has no reason to kill
Maid Kim,
How well do you know Moo Deok?
You know
What kind of life did she lead before she started working here?
What?
Killed -
the man I asked about Moo Deok's past
Bandits who may have been looking for her
dead too
Obviously she would come under suspicion
but she ran away instead of proving her innocence
What am I sure of -
Moo Deok is hiding something
what cannot be disclosed
The guards live over there
It would be faster
draw her portrait and look for her yourself
I don't know what she looks like
- I met her when I was still blind
- I thought you weren't
Now you say that you were blind, then you say that you were not
I don’t know what’s going on there, but your life is clearly not easy
So you don’t know her by sight, but she knows you?
Maybe it’s even dangerous to look for her?
What if it was she who killed those people?
And suddenly it will harm you
It's more dangerous to be a suspected leader
You can get hurt too, but you paid the merchant
That is?
I don't understand what you mean
Exactly
Pretend you don't know anything
Someone died!
Guard Li and Guard Chan!
Hwangsu will give you incredible strength
I thought all nomads were monsters
But you have gained youth and immortality
It's clear now
why did everyone want ice stone for alchemy?
Everyone was so thirsty for him, they were always fighting
Therefore this magic is forbidden
Okay, Master Li
You can recognize them
Look around
Are there any nomads in the palace?
Just looking at a person is not enough
If the blue mark is not visible
or signs of wildness,
they are indistinguishable from ordinary people
Then how do you recognize them?
Fear of being caught
Fear of petrification
We need to get this fear out
So you instill fear in them?
Sorry if I disappointed you
In return
I'll give you a gift
Gift? What's there?
Dog
Dog?
He is very smart and obedient
He is now standing at the gates of the palace
Can I bring him?
Since it's a gift, then of course
Bring the dog
Chan Wook
I want you to bring him
If you can handle it, I'll reward you
Should I just run away with Moo Deok?
Then everyone will understand
And now I am weak and will not protect my teacher
I wonder what Master Li is going to do?
Deputy
What is it?
Is this fluffy a gift from the master to the king?
Master Li said the dog will follow you
But be careful
What is the danger of taking him into the palace?
What's the matter?
This is Gwigu
He brought Gwiga to the palace
But Gwigu is a monster
How could he bring him to the palace?
My teacher Seo Kyung used Gwiga
to search for relics created by dark magic
using an ice stone
Yes I heard
But I thought it could no longer be used,
because his urn is broken
Therefore
I transferred Gwigu's soul into the body of a dead dog
The dog I brought
this is Gwigu
Gwiga?
What should we do?
How many of us are there in the palace?
More than ten
Transferred to Jeonbugwan?
Sent a man, they will arrive soon
This meeting is organized in order to establish peace between the magicians and the palace
The Crown Prince visited Sosnovy Bor, and honored you by inviting you here
Do you want to bring it here?
monster without asking His Majesty's permission?
He gave his permission
And now Gwigu
not a monster, because in the body of an ordinary dog
So, he won’t be able to harm the nomad even if he finds him?
He will start barking, so we will understand
Woof
Woof!
This is a nomad
As we thought, nomads in the palace
What's that sound?
So there are nomads in my palace?
Looks like it
Then why are you just standing here?
Go and catch him!
Like I said, the dog is a gift.
I'll leave it here
With its help you will find everyone
nomads in the palace
Take him away, we don't need him
How dare you bring this monster here?!
The king suffers from anxiety
Are you trying to harm him with this monster?
Mother, we ourselves invited Master Li to the palace
Don't get involved in this
It is Jeonbugwan's duty to protect the palace.
If dark magic was used in the palace,
they'll figure it out
I don't want to see a monster in a dog's body,
neither the people of Sosnovy Bor
You're trying to humiliate us
Stop them, Your Majesty
Gwangju Jeonbugwan's son must protect the palace,
and you brought this monster here
This is Master Li's gift to the king
Let us in
I was ordered to bring him
How's that?
Then try to come in
Kill this beast that has entered the palace
If you can handle it, I'll reward you
Is that why he asked me to bring the dog?
Your Majesty, this is Jin Mu
I'll get rid of these insolent people from Sosnovy Bor
We are here at his invitation, and we haven’t finished talking
Jin Moo, you shouldn't get involved in this.
How dare you bring this monster here without permission?!
What kind of behavior is this?!
Be silent
Guards! Don't stand there! Stop him!
Father
Stop them both
If a fight starts, our relationship will end
We must fight!
The pine forest brought this beast here!
Jeonbugwan must protect us
- Father!
- Your Majesty
I order everyone...
stop
Stop!
Master Li,
I invited you in a friendly manner, was it necessary to scare me like that?
Sorry
Your Majesty, if the ice stone is unsealed,
bloodshed will begin again
Ice stone?
Is it because of the nomads?
People used
reflectors for the alchemy of souls after the Great Chaos
Apparently someone is making reflectors again
Ice stone printed
And?
Where is he? In whose hands?
Perhaps it is with those
who sent Nak Su and turned the magician of Sosnovy Bor into a nomad
I heard Master Seo Kyung
destroyed all the ice stones 200 years ago
Apparently
not all were destroyed, some remained in Sosnovy Bor
It's not easy to curb human desires
But
return of the ice stone
marks the coming of a man like Master Seo Kyung
Master So Kyung was born under the star of the King
However, he did not become king
Do you want to say
Is there anyone else born under this star?
Even if it exists, its light will be weak
And the energy of the seven stars that surround him has not yet manifested itself
A force that can withstand nature,
and bring chaos to the world, awakened again
There will be someone who will stop it
Like this
balance will be maintained in the world
What I'm saying is there's no point in worrying
I hope this brings you peace
Thanks for your words
Now I have to go
You refused my gift
so I'll take Gwiga with me
- Your Majesty
- Do as you wish
No, wait
Are we leaving?
I saw everything I wanted
So there are nomads in my palace?
Take him away, we don't need him
How dare you bring this monster here?!
They showed themselves when I gave them fear
Scared?
Not injured?
How did you get hurt?
The dog is fine, but I'm not, because of you
Got hurt?
I got hurt when I fought with those bandits, right?
He's got a long way to go, right?
Wait, that's blood. Hurt?
This is my blood
He wasn't hurt at all...
- Blood...
- You're covered in it
Well that's good
Does it hurt?
Apparently yes
It hurts...
Gwigu belongs to Master Li
How much does he know about Moo Deok?
And what will Uk do?
when will he find out about Nak Soo?
Are you okay?
All covered in cuts
I'm fine
Have you found the nomads? What about the stone?
You can't imagine...
My soul almost moved with horror
They staged a scene, but found no one?
Let the dog bite someone
Uk
Look for the nomad in the palace
more difficult than in Sosnovy Bor or Jeonbugwan
If things get out of hand,
a conflict will arise between the palace and Sosnovy Bor
Let's go
You need patching up
Master
Wait a little
The Crown Prince has asked to escort you to his palace.
- Crown Prince?
- It's going to rain
He wants you to wait for him
Lead
Uk, send it first
to Sosnovy Bor
Come here
Here
You should have told me that they were invited to the palace!
I thought this would be
regular meeting
If the queen
suffer, you will turn to stone like eunuch Kim
Useless piece of meat!
Someone born under the star of the King,
what will repeat the fate of Master So Kyung?
If it turns out that this star is the fruit of dark magic,
The end of the pine forest
I sent Gviga to Sosnovy Bor
Sorry for scaring you
When the nomad was found in Sosnovy Bor,
I thought that they might be in the palace too
Recently he even tried to get here
I heard that she created it
and killed Nak Soo
Nak Soo?
Mercenary who killed many warriors
Heads fly off the shoulders where she's been
That's why she's called that
There are rumors that she is a nomad and that she is alive
Nomad Nak Su?
Interesting rumors
I hope Moo Deok gets caught before the master returns
Moo Deok...
Why are you shaking?
Do you really believe that I killed someone?
Come in
Why did you come?
Take things and run away?
I came to ask for something
The head said to catch you as soon as you appear
Moo Deok,
You didn't do this, did you?
- Not me
-Then why did you run away?
I had to
Moo Deok
You have
any secrets?
Young Master
aware of them?
Moo Deok, you should run away
I'll give you money
Run and don't come back
I can't
I can't leave my master
Why?
If you stay close, he will also fall under suspicion.
If you're worried about him,
then help me
You don’t want to talk to the head, you don’t want to run away either
What will you do?
We need to find the killer
The killer kills those who know him by sight
Is this where Gwangju Jeonbugwan lives?
Apparently an influential family
Does anyone from the Chan family know you?
Wait around the corner. I'll bring this man
I want to ask someone to confirm
that I was not in the room when those people were killed
And who?
Mrs. Jin from Jinyeowon
I ran into her there
This sissy will not agree to meet you
Maid Kim
Take me to Jinyeowon
Jinyoewon?
Excuse me, can you help me lift the crutch?
Thank you
Won't you tell me where I am?
At Jeonbugwan's Gwangju House
I see
Thank you
Moo Deok
Let's go
Apparently Moo Deok can see now
But she didn't recognize me
I hope it's for the better
Why are you alone?
I was wrong. We don't know her at all
We're done. Let's return to Jeonbugwan
Can I try it?
- No
Stop it
I'm wet
This is that umbrella
This is an umbrella
Can be used as a cane
Mom will scold me, stop it
Enough is enough
- No way
- Hey
Would you like to trade umbrellas with me?
I heard Nak Soo moved
into the body of a tall, well-built young man
She could move into the body of a small, weak woman
With such a weak body, there would be no point in touching her.
But no
Nak Soo in blue was definitely a man
"Nak Soo in Blue"
- I heard about it
- He was dressed all in blue
It spread everywhere, people started wearing blue
They thought then
Nak Su in blue will protect them from the alchemy of souls
Nak Soo was a mercenary
but she didn’t kill ordinary people, and she didn’t have the strength
People can be so stupid
This is not stupidity
It's fear
Nak Soo's body was burned, everyone knows it
This is the work of the powerful and influential
Call them fools
when they're just scared, it's wrong
I brought you together in hopes of finding a solution,
but you have the nerve to sit here and criticize me
I understand that you want to humiliate each other,
but I hope we all start to get along
Master Li is also with us
Let's drink tea
Your Highness
What?
Lady Huo requests an audience
Let her in
What is it?
I heard someone got hurt after the fight
Came to check
Only one was injured here
- Take him away and treat him
- I'm fine
It won't be long
Come with me
Looks like Chan Wook will be engaged again
For the umpteenth time already?
- What does it mean?
- Don’t you know?
Do you really know nothing?
Rumors are circulating in Saejukwon
You three are potential candidates to be Master Ho Yeom's son-in-law
Uk is third on the list
But for her, apparently, he is the first
Ho Yeom wants to marry her off this year
Soon there will be talk of engagement. I assure you
The wounds are not deep. These pills will stop the bleeding
You should have given them to me right away
I heard about the wounds
I wanted to check it myself to calm down
Well...
You have been wounded more than once, so this thought arose...
I'm fine
Okay
Oh, exactly. Maid Kim gave it to me
I haven't thanked her yet
She's the same
Is it the same?
A hairpin that I saw twenty years ago
Oh, is this something valuable?
Looks new
Probably not ours
But it's done so similar
That's it
Apparently the prince was right
We'll hear about Wook's engagement soon
But for Master Huo he is third on the list
Will you marry her yourself, since you are the first on this list?
If you get married, you'll have to return to Seho
Yulia, just don’t get married. I'll be lonely
I can recognize nomads
We need to take it with us to Seho as soon as possible
Who?
Me?
I take my words back
I felt better after seeing your reaction today.
Glad to hear that
What did you want to ask me personally?
I know that you have the Nak Soo sword
Can I pick it up?
I saw the show last year
There were elephants there too
But when I go with Dan Gu, I have to pretend that it’s my first time there
So those tickets were for you and Mr. Dan Gu?
Scared me. What are you doing here?
I came to ask for a favor
About the service?
Don't bother
I have no desire to help you
I'm accused of murder
What?
You can go to the head of Sosnovy Bor
and say you saw me?
Do you want me to go to the head and admit that I went
to such a place?
I'm not crazy
You are my only hope
Please
No
I told Dan Gu that I have an extra ticket.
I don't want him to know where I bought them.
Your shame will be temporary
and they might kill me
If mom finds out, I won't live either.
She would never kill her daughter!
Why are you shouting when you came to ask for help?
Then I'll have to tell your mother everything myself.
and ask her for help
Should I ask my mom?
And here she is
You shouldn't have bothered with gifts to apologize for the past.
The more I think about it, the more I want to apologize
I'll go and ask her myself
Wait a minute
I'll think about it. First come with me
I'll be right back. Wait here
If you don't come back, I'll scream
- I'll be back
- Cho Young
Yes, mother
Wait
Very young
I wonder who it is?
Is it because of the incense?
Beautiful vase
If you put flowers in this vase, they will smell stronger
- Really?
- Yes
I have long wanted to change the vase in my daughter’s room
Thank you
Mother, will you put a vase in Boo Young unnie's room?
Flowers will smell stronger
Your sister is blind, so at least she can enjoy the smell of flowers
How dare you?!
What are you doing in my daughter's room?
She came with me
Probably lost
Moo Deok, what are you doing here?
Sorry
Help me just once
Go away
And don't come back anymore
Yes
I'll come. I promise
Cho Young,
tell the servants to clean your sister's room again
Yes, mother
So I
This man will be your father
Father?
Does a father want to bring a fake daughter into the house?
I am not Jin Bu Young's father by blood
Her real father is someone else
To be recognized as the daughter of the Jin family,
you must open the doors of Jinyoung
And for this, their blood must flow through your veins
What is this?
A worm containing the blood of a Jin family member
This is Cho Young's blood
my favorite
And what will you do about it?
Reach out your hand
Don't keep me waiting
Now you have the blood of the Jin family.
If I didn't use dark magic,
this worm will eat you from the inside
Trying to escape
this worm will eat you alive
This is the room of her daughter, who died 10 years ago.
Apparently she drowned
but Mrs. Jin still thinks she will come back
I feel sorry for her
Forgive her for the slap
Was her daughter blind?
Yes, I was
The owner of this body was also blind
Maybe that's why I felt something strange?
Master Li wanted to talk to the prince alone about something.
I see
The head asked to accompany you to Sosnovy Bor
Me? Why?
Come with us
They'll lock me up here again, right?
- What's happening?
- This...
We are told to be silent
Wait for him here
Moo Deok was seen next to the bodies, it's clear why she was taken away
But why, sir? He was in the palace
What is the boss thinking?
I don't know
Yul,
Moo Deok won't kill anyone
Really?
Can I look at the bodies?
The killer wielded the sword skillfully
This can't be Moo Deok
But she's Nak Soo
She could have killed them
I have my reasons
don't get in my way
- These are those bandits
- Do you know them?
I fought them not too long ago
Can I take their bodies and have a funeral?
What brought Chief Chwiseonra here?
Did someone die?
Our guards were killed
Dan Gu
Maid Kim spoke about what happened
Cho Young,
help Moo Deok
I went there to buy tickets
Moo Deok was there
Of course
It was my first time in such a place
I know
We talked for a while and then Moo Deok came in
I saw you too as you entered
Of course I didn't think I'd see you in a place like this
I know
Here's what happens...
Moo Deok would never have had the time to kill those men.
Recently a girl came to Jwiseonru looking for Moo Deok
She pretended to be a magician
Chief Chwisungru thinks
this could be So Yi, the girl the merchant warned Moo Deok about
I once saw a girl being dragged by these bandits
Merchant,
bandits and guards
They all crossed paths with this So Yi
This scammer So Yi is very suspicious
This means Moo Deok is not to blame.
Okay
I myself doubted that Moo Deok could kill anyone
That's it. You knew, uncle, that Moo Deok was not capable of this, right?
Can you let Wook and Moo Deok go now?
I locked them up to
ask something
I'll take care of the rest myself
You can go
Okay
Chapter
At least tell me what's wrong
Moo Deok committed murder
What...
She killed those who knew her in the past
Tell me what you and Moo Deok are hiding
If your words don't match Moo Deok's,
you won't leave this room
And Moo Deok will die
Chief, listen...
It's not about murder
Uk revealed your secret to me
He told everything
If you also tell the truth, I will spare your life
But if
your words will differ
you will die
If he knew that she was a nomad,
I wouldn't waste my time like this
He's trying to split us by interrogating us separately
We must say the same thing
What would Chan Wook answer?
A secret that we both are guaranteed to reveal
A secret whose disclosure will not lead to my death
I'll tell you
I confess to you
What happened?
Moo Deok and Chan Wook
you can let go
What did they say? One and the same?
They said... the same thing
- You came out
- You too
- Glad you're okay
- Me too
Thankfully we said the same thing
What did you say?
We both left...
so you said the same thing
You locked them up to find out what they were hiding
I think you've figured out something
Tell me
What's their secret there?
They...
literally left me speechless
They showed the same thing
I'll tell the truth
I tried not to get caught
This is what I was hiding
You see, I...
Actually I...
love Moo Deok
I love the owner very much
I thought you'd probably admit it
They wouldn't kill me for this
Yes, and in the Sosnovy Bor rule book there is nothing about this
There is no prohibition for a boy to love a girl
Yes
And a servant's love for her master will not lead to death
Is that what you said? Why do you love me to death?
Well...
I exaggerated so that he would believe
There was no other choice
There was no choice but to admit that you love me to death
I'm kind of sorry
I didn't put so much feeling into my confession.
I had to try
Forget it
Don't put everything on the line for something as fickle as love.
If this happens again,
and life will depend on the choice,
betray love
and choose life
Unless, of course, you want to die
This is the teacher's order
teacher,
what if I don't mind dying?
Can I then continue to love you?
In other words, I'm willing to risk it all
so that we can be together
I'll do so
Do the same, stick to your confession
Love me to death
Thanks for watching with us!
doramamania
Alchemy
Shower
If Uk falls in love with someone he shouldn't,
what will you do?
If I'm with you, I need to make sure that you're mine
How dare you disgrace Jinyeowon?
- Salty
- Two boots - a pair
Why didn't you get married?
I'm looking for shaman Choi
If the shaman was hunted by the magicians of Jeonbugwan...
Are you looking for her because she holds a grudge against your father?
If he comes, report immediately
Even dead, it's Gwigu
You pretend you don't know, right?
It was hard for you, right?
If you have to draw a sword and point it at someone,
let me be the first